So I got a mentor and I
actually paid this person $55,000 for the year,
but this person helped me scale my
business to over $5 million a year.
Let me ask you this, like, look,
what has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In all my companies combined, we've done
about $25 million total in a year.
In a single year, I want
to say we did $18 million.
Probably about $13 million.
This is actually going to be
our best year. We're looking at,
we're going to finish right about
eight figures, probably about like $10-11 million.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I own a marketing agency. That's my primary business.
I spent roughly $500,000 on learning to
sell, learning to market, going into masterminds.
I turned that into $33 million.
This year, I crossed the stage doing over
$25 million. I got the same watch on,
but it was a time in my
life where this watch meant everything to me.
When it comes to the way that people
look at money, what's the biggest difference that
separates the middle class from the wealthy?
The number one thing between the rich and the
poor when it comes to how they perceive money.
Hand me that bag. If I said I will
sell you this bag for $1,000, what would you say?
Probably yours.
Okay. That is how a poor
person thinks. A rich person would ask...
What's going on, everybody? We just landed in
Orlando, Florida, and we are at one of the
largest business conferences in the entire world.
This is Russell Brunson's Funnel Hacking Live,
where some of the biggest seven, eight,
and nine figure entrepreneurs are gathered here today.
We're going to be asking them how they
became millionaires, what they did to create wealth in
their industry, and how you can start
your path to becoming financially free in 2023.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year, probably about $13 million.
How long have you been a business owner for?
15 years.
I spent roughly $500,000
on learning to sell, learning to market, going
into masterminds. I turned that into $33 million.
When it comes to the way that people look
at money, what would you say is the biggest thing
that separates the middle class from those
who really end up building that wealth?
Okay. Hand me that bag. See this little bag right
here? If I said I will sell you this bag
for $1,000, what would you say?
Probably yours.
Okay. That is how a poor person thinks.
A rich person would ask, what's inside? Because what
if I had $100,000 in cash in this
bag? You just lost $99,000 because you simply didn't
ask what's inside. Rich people, they worry about what
they get, not what it costs. And when they
understand what they get, they understand what they
stand to lose. Poor people never ask what's
inside. They never ask what it's worth. They just
ask what it's cost. That's all they care about.
And that's why life goes
by and it costs them everything.
What would you say has been your secret
to sales though? How have you been able to
consistently sell tens of millions
of dollars throughout your career?
You want me to tell you how to
create a personal brand that sells in 30 seconds?
Yeah.
Okay. So here's what you do. First, what
is the most enduring personal brands of all time?
Superheroes.
Why superheroes? Because they clearly stand for and
against something. A strong brand is when you
know exactly what you stand for, exactly what you
stand against. You make a list of the top 10
superheroes. You list out what they stand for,
what they stand against. You can easily get this
list by asking ChadGBT. You pick the one that you
resonate with the most. Then you modify it to suit
you. I picked Iron Man. I changed it to
Iron Dan. Tweaked it. Now everything you say, everything you
do, it has to fall in alignment with
for or against. As long as you do that,
you can't not have a personal brand.
You literally have to have a personal brand,
even if you don't understand what a
personal brand is, because everything you say
fundamentally, fundamentally goes for or against
something. Like for instance, I'm against
ignorance. If you're a business owner and you
have never read the shareholder letters of Steve Jobs
to his company, if you've never watched Steve
Jobs' presentations, then I'm sorry, I don't take
you seriously as a business owner because you are
not even remotely trying hard enough to grow a
business. So like you're just a schmuck. I get that,
but if you do, then you're just a piece of shit.
And it's not just for the sake of it, you're
just a piece of shit. And if you're a business owner,
you're not even remotely trying hard enough to
grow a business. So like you're just a schmuck.
Wow.
Dan, my man.
That was phenomenal.
That interview right there has got to be
one of the craziest ones that I've ever done.
Not only is Dan an eight figure entrepreneur,
but the analogies that he used, he really
just put into perspective of
how a poor person really thinks.
They don't ask the right questions.
He made me look like a fool, but this
video is going to be absolutely insane, so stay
tuned because the best is yet to come.
This year I crossed the stage doing over 25 million.
I got the same watch on, but it was
a time in my life where this watch meant everything
to me.
How long have you been a business owner for?
I've been in the entrepreneur space since 2006.
Throughout your career as an entrepreneur, what
has been the most amount of money that
you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year, I want
to say we did 18 million.
Now I see the shirt, recession proof.
What's the blueprint to creating a recession proof business?
Because you can't control a pandemic.
You can't control when the economy goes to shit.
Everything has to make money three or four ways.
Any business that you have should
make money three or four ways.
So I tell people, listen,
it doesn't matter what you're in.
You should have at least four verticals to your business.
Always you should have a digital product.
You should have some kind of in-person event.
You should have the product or service or
whatever it is that you actually do and specialize
in.
I don't want to be in some kind of
program where it's like an apprentice program or a
high level mentorship that's 25, 50K.
It doesn't mean that you have to make millions off
of each, but just say you got a 50K mentorship
program and you take four people a year.
That's an extra $200,000 to your
business revenue to your bottom dollar.
So those are things that you want to
be mindful of when you're actually building your business.
As an eight figure entrepreneur, what's been
the best financial advice that you ever received
throughout your career?
Wealth is not determined by dollar amount.
Wealth is determined by the way that you're structured.
See what wealthy is that you can make
a hundred thousand dollars a year and build wealth.
You don't need to make millions.
It's not a dollar amount.
Like I got to go make X amount.
You have to realistically, it's a numbers game
and a percentage game and a growth game.
If you can make a hundred thousand dollars a
year and you can save, you know, 25% of
it, 20% of it, but then you also, the
part that you spend, Hey, I got a mortgage, but
you know, my real estate portfolio where
I'm investing into real estate, how much equity
is it is growing is my investment
portfolio, my insurance, the income that I make.
If I can divide it properly, this
is the way that we make wealth.
It's not a dollar amount that I
have to go out and generate per year.
It's what I do.
With the money.
That's what separates everybody.
The difference with the middle class and the
wealthy is that they get educated on all of
these different verticals.
So that way they can make
sound decisions when it comes to it.
Marcus, that was phenomenal, bro.
Shout out to my guy, Marcus, man.
He's one of the most
inspiring entrepreneurs that I've ever interviewed.
And he's got a business that's
going to do $18 million this year.
You saw the t-shirt man recession proof.
If you're going to create a business, it's
got to last beyond no matter what's happening
to the outside world and the economy.
Let's go get this next one, man.
Orlando has been crazy.
We'll keep it rolling.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career?
I own a marketing agency.
That's my primary business.
And I basically run ads on social media
and pretty much anytime you click on anything
and you buy it on your
phone, it's because of me right here.
In the last 12 months, how
much money is your business generated?
In all my companies combined,
we've done about $25 million total.
When it comes to the way that people look
at money, what would you say is the biggest
thing that separates the middle class from
those who really do end up building that
generational wealth and becoming financially free?
The number one thing between the rich and
the poor when it comes to how they perceive
money is the poor want
to want to keep their money.
It's like acorns, like squirrels.
They take all these acorns.
They put it in their pockets.
They put it in a tree.
There's only so much fucking room in this
tree for acorns at the end of the day.
The rich people do the opposite.
They take their money and they find ways.
They treat them like an army of soldiers, right?
Every dollar is a soldier and they go put
that soldier out to go and make more money
at the end of the day and multiply.
And I've never been scared the last five to
six years to go and spend all the money I
have to go build more businesses, to go
make investments in my future, in my brain, in
my company, whatever it is.
Whereas I see all my friends that stay in
the same spot, as much money as they make,
they sit there and they hoard
and they always play on defense.
And I'll tell you this, whoever's listening,
you'll look back in 20, 30 years.
If you play your whole life on defense, saving
and just trying to cut costs and cut corners,
you'll look back and you'll really
regret how you played your life.
I think if you play your
life on offense, you're a go-getter.
You try to fucking shoot big,
play big, roll the dice on yourself.
I think you'll be a lot
happier with the decisions that you make.
For somebody who is stuck in that cycle
of poverty, what are some actionable first steps
that they can take to really get serious
about creating the life that they want for themselves
and becoming financially free?
I'm going to give you a story.
When I was 21, I was making
about 150K a year in a sales job.
I quit that sales job to
go work a 30K a year job.
And the reason I did that was because I understood.
At that age, I could learn.
I could invest in my brain and I
could learn enough information from 21 to 29
that just in year 30 alone, I can make
more money than all my friends made those nine years.
And so the problem is when you're young,
you see a lot of people making money
and you want to chase money.
You want to find a job that's paying more.
You want to do all these
things and just chase money, money, money.
But at the end of the day, if
you change that perspective and you chase knowledge,
information, skill sets for that, you know,
especially that beginning part of your life,
when you get to the age of 30,
you can make more money in that one year
than you made the last nine years
and your friends made the last nine years.
And it's only going to keep.
It's compounding.
So take every bit of time that you have,
every dollar that you have at a young age,
invest in knowledge, information,
masterminds, YouTube video, online courses.
Don't listen to your friends.
That shit is not a scam, dude.
That shit has absolutely changed my life.
And in this last 12 months, I've made
more money than I have the last nine years
of working every single day because
of those skills that compounded over time.
Give me that shit, bro.
All right, final thing.
If you're sitting on your couch
right now, you're sitting in your car,
wherever the fuck you are watching this video right now,
and you're not where you want to
be in life, you've got to understand,
you've got to look yourself in the
fucking mirror and know it's all on you.
It's on no one else out here.
So get your ass.
Get your ass off the phone.
Open up some books.
Watch some courses.
And get your ass in the game.
And let's start making some dollars, baby.
Peace.
That interview with Eddie was absolutely insane.
His business is going to do
$20 to $25 million this year.
And his analogy about the acorns was
one of the craziest that I've ever heard.
Rich people do not hoard their money.
They make it work for them.
Shout out to Eddie.
Let's go get this next
one and keep this video rolling.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
This is going on my eighth year.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
So what I do is I
teach individuals and entrepreneurs how to start,
grow, or scale any business by way of leveraging credit.
So I created a software.
That leverages Metro to
compliance with artificial intelligence.
And anybody, no matter what your credit scores look like,
what's on your credit profile, you can use
this software with a click of a button.
It uploads your credit profile.
And it'll do all of the work for you, bro.
What's the number one
lesson you've learned about entrepreneurship
that you pass on to someone
that they cannot learn in school?
I think that we all fool from a society standpoint
that we feel like college is like the way to go.
But it's like when you look at
it, you're learning from somebody that's making,
what, $40,000 to $60,000 a year.
So that means that they can only teach
you how to make $40,000 to $60,000 a year.
So what I realized is that when I graduated college,
that I didn't get the right knowledge and information
that I needed to be a entrepreneur.
So I got a mentor, and I
actually paid this person $55,000 for the year.
But this person helped me scale my
business to over $5 million a year.
That's incredible.
Let me ask you this.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year, this is
actually going to be our best year.
We're looking at, we're going
to finish by about eight figures,
probably about like $10,000, $11,000 million.
Give a credit hack to the people out there.
What's one thing that people don't
know about how they can use credit
to really generate wealth and become, you know?
Yeah, one simple thing that most people don't
know about is you can add trade lines.
Trade lines, which is considered
authorized users to your credit profile.
And it'll boost up your
credit profile because it's positive.
It's positively affecting four out
of your five credit metrics.
So we're talking about adding a line of credit.
Let's say you own.
I add it to my credit profile.
Let's say if it's a 20-year, $10,000 Discover card, right?
If I add that to my credit profile, then it
boosts me up from, let's say, a $600 to a $700.
Now I can go with access
to $50,000 to $100,000 in credit.
So now I can go start
and grow and scale my business.
You crushed that shit, man.
Let's go, bro.
We're going to go crazy.
We're going to go viral, man.
Let's go.
I love it.
This video was absolutely insane, but
I want you to like and subscribe
for some amazing content coming soon.
And click here to watch us going all
over Miami asking multimillionaires how they became wealthy.